{
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Who is the main character in Disney's \"Up?\"",
            "choice1": "Ellie",
            "choice2": "Russel",
            "choice3": "Dug",
            "answer": "Carl Fredricksen"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is the movie \"Up,\" based on?",
            "choice1": "Anne Hathaway",
            "choice2": "Elizabeth Docter",
            "choice3": "Elizabeth Stallworth-Allen",
            "answer": "Edith Macefield"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 2 + 2?",
            "choice1": "5",
            "choice2": "Fish",
            "choice3": "Red",
            "answer": "4"
        },{
            "question": "What is the technical name of our sun?",
            "choice1": "Antares",
            "choice2": "Vega",
            "choice3": "Betelgeuse",
            "answer": "Sol"
        },{
            "question": "What is the name of our Moon?",
            "choice1": "Lovegood",
            "choice2": "Europa",
            "choice3": "Io",
            "answer": "Luna"
        },{
            "question": "What is the biggest planet in our Solar System?",
            "choice1": "Saturn",
            "choice2": "Mars",
            "choice3": "Europa",
            "answer": "Jupiter"
        },{
            "question": "What state is Salt Lake City in?",
            "choice1": "Idaho",
            "choice2": "Nevada",
            "choice3": "Ireland",
            "answer": "Utah"
        },{
            "question": "What does a baby computer call his father?",
            "choice1": "Dad",
            "choice2": "Father",
            "choice3": "Dada",
            "answer": "Data"
        },{
            "question": "After an unsuccessful harvest, why did the farmer decide to try a career in music?",
            "choice1": "Because he had a ton of sick corn.",
            "choice2": "Because he had a ton of sick apples.",
            "choice3": "Because....",
            "answer": "Because he had a ton of sick beets."
        },{
            "question": "What brand of underwear do scientists wear?",
            "choice1": "Calvin Klein",
            "choice2": "Fruit of the loom",
            "choice3": "Uranus",
            "answer": "Kelvin Klein."
        }
    ]
}